That woman has the attention span
of a gnat.
Hey, Leonard. Sheldon says
you're going to the North Pole.
(Leonard:)Yeah. Pretty cool, huh?
(Penny:)Yeah, I'm just a little surprised
you didn't tell me.
(Leonard:)Well, it all happened kind of fast.
(Leonard:)And we had to get physicals
and buy thermal underwear...
(Leonard:)...and study up on, you know,
snow and stuff.
(Leonard:)- Sorry, I was gonna tell you.
- No, you don't have to apologize.
(Penny:)There's no reason you have to tell me.
I was just surprised.
(Sheldon:)You were busy, you were surprised,
all very fascinating.
(Sheldon:)Now, where do we stand
on the freezer?
(Penny:)Is he serious?
(Leonard:)Actually, it would help.
(Penny:)All right, I'll see what I can do.
So, wow, three months
at the North Pole.
(Penny:)- Wow, that is awesome.
- Yeah.
(Sheldon:)Sorry but at what point do you put this
"see what you can do" plan into action?
(Penny:)Just a warning, Sheldon.
The freezer locks from the outside.